<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English home on Homepathy</title>
    <link>https://similimum.info/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English home on Homepathy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://similimum.info/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me - Homeopathy in Dénia, Orba and Pedreguer</title>
      <link>https://similimum.info/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://similimum.info/en/about/</guid>
      <description>About me I was born in 1980 in Bielefeld, Germany. On account of my own disease, at the age of 13 I already had contact with natural therapies, among them homeopathy. Thanks to a breakthrough with the homeopathic treatment I am able to enjoy my life to the fullest.
In Germany I completed an intensive course encompassing conventional medicine and homeopathy. In 2012 I passed my exam before the public health department.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Applications - Homeopathy in Dénia, Orba and Pedreguer</title>
      <link>https://similimum.info/en/applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://similimum.info/en/applications/</guid>
      <description>Applications One of the frequent questions is “Is there something for my joints?” Or “Can you treat my back pain?” And similar questions about a whole host of other conditions like hypertension, migraine, heartburn, irritable bowel syndrome, rashes, anxiety, depression, insomnia etc. and symptoms that couldn’t be diagnosed.
The answer is: generally yes! Most conditions can be treated with homeopathy. How far an improvement can go and whether the disease can be cured depends on the individual person.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>